Which button type did you like most and least?
On Table:
-Best: Drag Circle
-Worst: Timer
On Hand:
-Best: Timer
-Worst: Drag Circle
Which display type did you like most and least?
Best: PCD with green text
Worst: PCD
Could you imagine playing card games in Virtual Reality?
Yes (interesting / special); cards alone boring (card games in reality boring)
What kind of other application could this interface be used for?
Second life; disabled people; voice input; animations for disabled people; control only via head movement; higher resolution
Read books; next page