Which button type did you like most and least?
-Best: Timer button; Easiest to select; fastest
-Worst: 
On Hand: Drag Circle; On hand you select wrong one without purpose
On Table: Three dots; Dots empty themselves too fast; 
Which display type did you like most and least?
Table display; Green text best readable (if green and far away)
What kind of other application could this interface be used for?
Virtual shop