Which button type did you like most and least?
On Table:
-Best: Three dots; Simplest
-Worst: Drag Circle; Most difficult
On Hand:
-Best: Three dots;
-Worst: Drag Circle
Which display type did you like most and least?
Best: PCD with text
Worst: PCD
Could you imagine playing card games in Virtual Reality?
No.
What kind of other application could this interface be used for?
Virtual museum;