Which button type did you like most and least?
On Table:
-Best: Arrows
-Worst: Drag circle (focus on circle easily lost)
On Hand:
-Best: Timer
-Worst: Drag Circle
Which display type did you like most and least?
Best: PCD
Worst: PCDtext (good to read;missing reference to card)
Could you imagine playing card games in Virtual Reality?
Yes.
What kind of other application could this interface be used for?
tutorial; manuals