Which button type did you like most and least?
On Table:
-Best: Drag Circle; Easily understandable (reminds of the sperrbildschirm of the iphone)
-Worst: Three Arrows; Empty field => you do not know what to do at first
On Hand:
-Best: Timer; Hand and eye movement difficult; static solution works better
-Worst: Drag Circle; Dragging too difficult
Which display type did you like most and least?
Best: Player-Centered Display; Card has good size; well positioned; (fixed angle: annoying as you have
to move your head)
Worst: fixed angle PCD with text; übersichtlich, but: only text
Could you imagine playing card games in Virtual Reality?
Yes, guess that's fun!
What kind of other application could this interface be used for?
---