Which button type did you like most and least?
-Best: Timer button; Simple to use, easy to abort;
-Worst: Three dots; too slow, too much accuracy needed
Which display type did you like most and least?
Table display; Green text best readable (if green and far away)
Player-centered display: Problems reading; Blurred, too close
Could you imagine playing card games in Virtual Reality?
Yes, but mostly because of fascinating technology! Probably not every day, as it gets boring.
What kind of other application could this interface be used for?
Schafkopf App;