Which button type did you like most and least?
On Table:
-Best: Arrows; Most logical
-Worst: Three Dots; Does not make sense
On Hand:
-Best: Timer; Easiest because static
-Worst: Three dots
Which display type did you like most and least?
Best: PCD fixed angle + PCD fixed angle with text; optisch gut, realitätsnah, wie buch öffnen; karte würdest du auch so anschaun
Worst: Table display; closing is bad
Could you imagine playing card games in Virtual Reality?
Would be fun. During driving a vehicle
What kind of other application could this interface be used for?
desktop applications; writing with hand in VR