Which button type did you like most and least?
On Table:
-Best: Arrows; Flüssig
-Worst: Three Dots; Leicht daneben treffen
On Hand:
-Best: Drag Circle
-Worst: Timer; Kleinsten
Which display type did you like most and least?
Best: PCD fixed angle <=> Table display
Worst: PCD
Could you imagine playing card games in Virtual Reality?
No, I don't like card games in general.
What kind of other application could this interface be used for?
Menu
Present object-specific properties. Language learning; Tutorials